Guide to the Owego and Ithaca Turnpike Company records, 1808-1936.
Owego and Ithaca Turnpike Company records, 1808-1936.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Owego and Ithaca Turnpike Company records, 1808-1936.
2005
Owego and Ithaca Turnpike Company.
.2 cubic ft.
Articles of agreement, correspondence, notes, account books, and stock certificates.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Articles of agreement, correspondence, notes, account books, and stock certificates pertaining to the Owego and Ithaca Turnpike Company.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Articles of agreement, correspondence, notes, account books, and stock certificates pertaining to the Owego and Ithaca Turnpike Company.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Owego and Ithaca Turnpike Company.
Subjects:
Toll roads--New York (State); Transportation--New York (State)
Form and Genre Terms:
Account books.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Link to a partial finding aid that has the list of Stock Certificates.
  Not all the material in the collection is covered by this guide.
- Articles of Agreement, 1808 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Notes and Articles of Agreement, 1809 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Notes and Articles of Agreement, 1810 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Notes and Agreements, 1811 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Notes, Agreements, Correspondence, 1813 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Notes, Articles of Agreement, Correspondence, 1821-1836 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Lewis Beers Certificates, 1814-1815 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Memorandum - Account Book - Second Gate, 1810-1813 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Account Book - North Gate, 1811 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Account Book - Middle Gate, 1811-1817 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Repair Book, 1813-1814 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- North Gate Book, 1814-1818 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Turnpike Account Book, 1817-1818 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Turnpike Account Book, 1817-1826 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Stock Certificates (single & double), 1809-1813 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Detailed list available in accession folder.
- Stock Certificates (triple), 1810-1814 (Box 1, Folder 16)